Finding Aid for the Jan Williams Collection of Images, 1962-2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Jan Williams and others, 1966-2007, II; Item 34-321
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano with Lukas Foss at the piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-303)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-304)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-305)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-306)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-307)
  - Inside of piano, prepared for John Cage's Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-308)
  - John Cage examining percussion instruments before rehearsal of his Concerto for Prepared Piano, with Coni Burnham and Diane Williams in background, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-309)
  - John Cage and John Rowland looking ovr percussion part at rehearsal of Cage's Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-310)
  - Diane Williams at rehearsal of John Cage's Concerto for Prepared Piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-311)
  - Merce Cunningham portrait with reflection in mirror, inscribed to Jan Williams, 1973, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-312)
  - Portrait of Carol Plantamura, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-313)
  - Bent Lylloff and Yvar Mikashoff on a couch at Jan and Diane Williams' house (63 Anderson Place, Buffalo, New York), 1989, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-314)
  - Diane Williams, Carol Plantamura, Renee Levine, and Sylvia Dimiziani on a couch at Jan and Diane Williams' house (63 Anderson Place, Buffalo, New York), 1989, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-315)
  - Bent Lylloff on a couch at Jan and Diane Williams' house (63 Anderson Place, Buffalo, New York), 1989, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-316)
  - John Boudler in a chair at Jan and Diane Williams' house (63 Anderson Place, Buffalo, New York), 1989, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-317)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and Fred Cohen at Jan and Diane Williams' house (63 Anderson Place, Buffalo, New York), undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-318)
  - Aki Takahashi and Frances-Marie Uitti at a reception following memorial concert for Yvar Mikhashoff, 1994-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-319)
  - Erik Oña conducting at a rehearsal for Yvar Mikhashoff's The Windwife, 1994-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-320)
  - Poster for UB Creative Associates, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-321)
- Slides, 1967-1974, III.; Item 322-375
  - Douglas Davis, Ed Yadzinski, and Bent Lylloff looking at a poster in Copenhagen, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-322)
  - Douglas Davis, Lukas Foss, and others exiting a plane in Warsaw, Poland, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-323)
  - Poster for Creative Associates concert in Warsaw, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-324)
  - Poster for Creative Associates concert in Warsaw, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-325)
  - Ed Yadzinski playing piano on stage during Warsaw Autumn Festival, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-326)
  - Douglas Davis, Ed Yadzinski, and Lukas Foss dining at a table, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-327)
  - Bent Lylloff with Claus B. Jensen and his son outside of the Lylloff Musikstudie, 1967, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-328)
  - Setting up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-329)
  - Musicians preparing for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-330)
  - Setting up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-331)
  - Setting up percussion for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-332)
  - Setting up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-333)
  - Setting up percussion for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-334)
  - Setting up inside the tent for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-335)
  - Setting up inside the tent for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-336)
  - Ed Yadzinski playing clarinet outside during set-up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-337)
  - George Ritscher, Marie Yadzinski, Diane Williams, Brian Israel, and one unidentified person outside the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-338)
  - Francis Miroglio and Ed Yadzinski talking during set-up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-339)
  - Two unidentified people walking outside the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-340)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-341)
  - New Percussion Quartet rehearsing in old Baird Hall, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-342)
  - Jan Williams at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Robert, Jacques (Box 3, Item JW-343)
  - George Ritscher at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-344)
  - Jesse Levine at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-345)
  - Jesse Levine and Ed Yadzinski at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-346)
  - Portrait of Jesse Levine at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-347)
  - Jesse Levine walking outside at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-348)
  - Lukas Foss and Ed Yadzinski at the set-up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-349)
  - Charles Haupt assisting with set-up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-350)
  - Two unidentified people walking outside at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-351)
  - Lukas Foss and Charles Haupt assisting with set-up for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-352)
  - Portrait of Ed Yadzinski with his clarinet at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-353)
  - Setting up inside the tent for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-354)
  - Ed Yadzinski playing his clarinet outside at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-355)
  - Setting up inside the tent for the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-356)
  - Jesse Levine and Charles Haupt walking outside at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-357)
  - Ed Yadzinski setting up inside the tent at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-358)
  - Jan Williams and Ed Yadzinski setting up inside the tent at the Nuits de la Fondation Maeght, 1970: L'Art vivant aux tats-Unis, 1970-07, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-359)
  - Percussionist Dennis Kahle writing at stop during concert tour with Creative Associates, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-360)
  - Poster for Semana de nueva musica, presented by the Creative Associates, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-361)
  - Jan Williams sitting on a fountain, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-362)
  - Renée Levine standing by a fountain, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-363)
  - Two unidentified people sitting on a bench, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-364)
  - Kiosk in Karlsrühe covered in posters, including several for the Creative Associates concert, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-365)
  - Inside the concert venue at the Gulbenkian Foundation, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-366)
  - Image of a crucifixion in the Galleria nazionale dell'Umbria, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-367)
  - Sale Maggiore in the Galleria nazionale dell'Umbria, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-368)
  - Dennis Kahle, Joseph Patkowski, and Jan Williams standing by a monument iin Warsaw's Old Town Market Square (Rynek Starego Miasta), 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-369)
  - Lejaren Hiller and Dennis Kahle in front of a billboard with poster for a concert by Jan Williams and Dennis Kahle at the Filharmonia Narodowa in Warsaw, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-370)
  - Poster for a concert by Jan Williams and Dennis Kahle at the Filharmonia Narodowa in Warsaw, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-371)
  - Galleria nazionale dell'Umbria portale maggiore, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-372)
  - Lejaren Hiller and guide outside of a hat store in Warsaw, 1974-03, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-373)
  - Dennis Kahle and guide at a monument in Warsaw's Old Town Market Square (Rynek Starego Miasta), 1974-04, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-374)
  - Jan Williams and guide by a monumnet in Warsaw's Old Town Market Square (Rynek Starego Miasta), 1974-04, 1 35 mm. slide; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 3, Item JW-375)
- Additional prints, 1988-2001, IV; Item 376-548
  Arranged in chronological order and then in order of receipt
  - Unidentified man, John Boudler, and Jan Williams dining in São Paulo, 1988-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-376)
  - Carlos Stasi and John Boudler standing outside in São Paulo, 1988-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-377)
  - Jan Williams and Carlos Stasi outside in São Paulo, 1988-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-378)
  - Jan Williams with Bent Lyllof, Gideon Steiner, and Dave Weckl at a reception in Lyllof's house following Williams' induction as an honorary member into the Danish Percussion Society, 1989-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-379)
  - Jan and Diane Williams at a reception in Bent Lyllof's house following Williams' induction as an honorary member into the Danish Percussion Society, 1989-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-380)
  - Bent Lylloff, President of the Danish Percussion Society, shaking hands with Jan Williams, being inducted as an honorary member, 1989-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-381)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann sitting beside her work, De Consolatione Philosophiae, 1995, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-382)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann and Eberhard Blum eating, 1995, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-383)
  - Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams eating, 1995, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-384)
  - Jan Williams, John Patrick Thomas, Gudrun Reschke, Eberhard Blum, Iven Hausmann, and Robert Black in the garden of the Akademie der Künste, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-385)
  - Stage setup for John Cage's Ryoanji in the Akademie der Künste, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-386)
  - Jan Williams, John Patrick Thomas, Gudrun Reschke, Eberhard Blum, Iven Hausmann, and Robert Black during rehearsal of for John Cage's Ryoanji in the Akademie der Künste, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-387)
  - Jan Williams outside of the Reichstag, which had been wrapped by the artist, Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-388)
  - Jan Williams and Robert Black in front of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-389)
  - Jan Williams and Robert Black in front of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-390)
  - Jan Williams outside of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-391)
  - Jan Williams and Ann Holyoke Lehmann ouside of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-392)
  - Eberhard Blum, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Jan Williams in front of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-393)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Werner Uehlinger in front of the Reichstag, wrapped by Christo, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-394)
  - Christo's Wrapped Reichstag, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-395)
  - Jan Williams, John Patrick Thomas, Robert Black, and Eberhard Blum eating at a restaurant outdoors, 1995-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-396)
  - Nils Vigeland on stage at the Berlnische Galerie before a performance of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-397)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-398)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-399)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-400)
  - Jan Williams preparing his marimba for a performance of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-401)
  - Nils Vigeland and Eberhard Blum at the piano before a performance of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-402)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-403)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-404)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-405)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman (on loan from the Des Moines Art Center) being hung in the Berlinische Galerie, with Nils Vigeland watching from the piano, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-406)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing for Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-407)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing for Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-408)
  - Jan Williams at his marimba for a rehearsal of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-409)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams at rehearsal of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-410)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams at rehearsal of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-411)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams at rehearsal of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-412)
  - Eberhard Blum rehearsing Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-413)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-414)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-415)
  - Philip Guston's portrait of Morton Feldman hung at the Berlinische Galerie, 1996-01, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-416)
  - Jan Williams, Graciela Paraskevaídis, Coriún Aharonián, Joel Chadabe, Ricardo Gomez, and Jorge Camiruaga eating outdoors at a restaurant in Montevideo, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-417)
  - Jan Williams with Joel Chadabe bowing after a performance of one of Chadabe's works, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-418)
  - Joel Chadabe and Jan Williams, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-419)
  - Coriún Aharonián, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-420)
  - Graciela Paraskevaídis, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-421)
  - Jorge Camiruaga, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-422)
  - Joel Chadabe, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-423)
  - Jan Williams on a street in Montevideo, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-424)
  - Francisco Kröpfl outside of the Centro Cultural Recoleta, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-425)
  - Francisco Kröpfl, Jan Williams, and unidentified man on a street in Buenos Aires, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-426)
  - Jan Williams and Joel Chadabe in front of Auditorio El Aleph of the Centro Cultural Recoleta (Buenos Aires, Argentina), 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-427)
  - Jan Williams and Joel Chadabe in front of Auditorio El Aleph of the Centro Cultural Recoleta (Buenos Aires, Argentina), 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-428)
  - Jan Williams seated on ferry between Montevideo and Buenos Aires, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-429)
  - Jan Williams and Joel Chadabe with students in Montevideo, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-430)
  - Jan Williams after a concert in Montevideo, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-431)
  - Jan Williams and Joel Chadabe with students in Montevideo, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-432)
  - Diane Williams at Igor Stravinsky's grave in Venice, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Jan, 1939- (Box 4, Item JW-433)
  - Jan Williams at the Forum in Rome, 1997, 1 photograph; Williams, Diane (Box 4, Item JW-434)
  - Jan and Diane Williams eating at Richard Trythall's rooftop garden, 1997, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-435)
  - Jan and Diane Williams, and Eberhard Blum on a boat in Berlin, 1997, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-436)
  - Jan and Diane Williams on a bridge in Berlin, 1997, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-437)
  - Jan and Diane Williams, and Eberhard Blum outside of the Altes Museum in Berlin, 1997, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 4, Item JW-438)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Nils Vigeland before a performance of Morton Feldman's Why Patterns?, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-439)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, Nils Vigeland, and Ann Holyoke Lehmann before a performance of Morton Feldman's Why Patterns?, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-440)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Han de Vries rehearsing Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-441)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Han de Vries rehearsing Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-442)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Han de Vries rehearsing Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-443)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Han de Vries rehearsing Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-444)
  - Han de Vries and Eberhard Blum at a rehearsal of Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-445)
  - Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams at a rehearsal of Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-446)
  - Han de Vries, Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams at a rehearsal of Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-447)
  - Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and Han de Vries at a rehearsal of Morton Feldman's Instruments 3, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-448)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's Crippled Symmetry, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-449)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's Crippled Symmetry, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-450)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's Crippled Symmetry, 1997-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-451)
  - Jorge Camiruaga and Diane Williams sitting by the ocean in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-452)
  - Jan Williams and Jorge Camiruaga in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-453)
  - Jan Williams and Jorge Camiruaga eating outdoors in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-454)
  - Jan Williams and two students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-455)
  - Jorge Camiruaga teaching students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-456)
  - Jan Williams and Jorge Camiruaga teaching students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-457)
  - Jan Williams teaching students in Montevideo, 1997-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 4, Item JW-458)